export const ApiQuestion =
    [
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506d6",
            "correctAnswer": "Uma Thurman",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Pen√©lope Cruz",
                "Kirsten Dunst",
                "Kristin Scott Thomas"
            ],
            "question": "Which actor has featued in films including Pulp Fiction and Kill Bill Volume 1?",
            "tags": [
                "cult_films",
                "film",
                "acting",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "62573fbc9da29df7b05f73a9",
            "correctAnswer": "Once Upon a Time in America",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Goodfellas",
                "Gone with the Wind",
                "There Will Be Blood"
            ],
            "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A former gangster returns home, where he must confront the regrets of his old life.'",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c83",
            "correctAnswer": "Sabrina, Kelly, Jill",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Ashley, Michelle, Tina",
                "Joan, Lucy, Emily",
                "Mary, Louise, Jackie"
            ],
            "question": "What were the character names of the 3 lead women of Charlie's Angels?",
            "tags": [
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "62573eef9da29df7b05f737e",
            "correctAnswer": "Schindler's List",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "The Bridge on the River Kwai",
                "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest",
                "Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind"
            ],
            "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A man becomes concerned for his Jewish workforce after witnessing their persecution by the Nazis.'",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb11",
            "correctAnswer": "Jodie Foster",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Glenn Close",
                "Melanie Griffith",
                "Meryl Streep"
            ],
            "question": "Who won the 1988 Academy Award for Best Leading Actress for playing the role of Sarah Tobias in The Accused?",
            "tags": [
                "academy_awards",
                "acting",
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fc16",
            "correctAnswer": "\"As God is my witness, I'll never be hungry again.\"",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "\"With great power comes great responsiblity.\"",
                "\"Forget it, Jake, it's Chinatown.\"",
                "\"I am Groot.\""
            ],
            "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'Gone with the Wind'?",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "quotes",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbed",
            "correctAnswer": "\"I'll get you, my pretty, and your little dog, too!\"",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "\"Release the Kraken!\"",
                "\"I love lamp.\"",
                "\"Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn.\""
            ],
            "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film 'The Wizard of Oz'?",
            "tags": [
                "quotes",
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "62573fbf3d2f5c16bfb8833b",
            "correctAnswer": "Inglourious Basterds",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Hotel Rwanda",
                "Snatch",
                "Cool Hand Luke"
            ],
            "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'During World War II, a group of Jewish U.S. soldiers plan to assassinate Nazi leaders.'",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f8b9",
            "correctAnswer": "Vivien Leigh",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Holly Hunter",
                "Whoopi Goldberg",
                "Bette Davis"
            ],
            "question": "Which actress played the role of Scarlett O'Hara in Gone with the Wind?",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "acting",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f9506fa",
            "correctAnswer": "Matthew McConaughey",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Ryan Reynolds",
                "Jim Carrey",
                "Hugh Jackman"
            ],
            "question": "Which actor has starred in films including Interstellar and Dallas Buyers Club?",
            "tags": [
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb40",
            "correctAnswer": "Forrest Gump",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Four Weddings and a Funeral",
                "Pulp Fiction",
                "Quiz Show"
            ],
            "question": "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1994?",
            "tags": [
                "academy_awards",
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "6257403f9da29df7b05f73cf",
            "correctAnswer": "A withdrawn boy who communicates with spirits seeks the help of a child psychologist.",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "A secretly ruthless woman insinuates herself into the lives of an aging actor and her circle of theater friends.",
                "A stand-up comedian embarks on a downward spiral that leads to the creation of an iconic villain.",
                "A former Roman General seeks revenge against the emperor who murdered his family."
            ],
            "question": "What is the plot of the movie The Sixth Sense?",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f910",
            "correctAnswer": "Jack Nicholson",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Samuel L. Jackson",
                "Peter O'Toole",
                "Bruce Willis"
            ],
            "question": "Which actor played the role of Jack Torrance in The Shining?",
            "tags": [
                "acting",
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94f924",
            "correctAnswer": "Broadcast News",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "The Birds",
                "Mad Max",
                "Fatal Attraction"
            ],
            "question": "Which film contains the character 'Jane Craig'?",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "fictitious_characters",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb5f",
            "correctAnswer": "My Fair Lady",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Becket",
                "Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb",
                "Mary Poppins"
            ],
            "question": "Which film won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 1964?",
            "tags": [
                "academy_awards",
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fada",
            "correctAnswer": "Adrien Brody",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Nicolas Cage",
                "Michael Caine",
                "Daniel Day-Lewis"
            ],
            "question": "Who won the 2002 Academy Award for Best Leading Actor for playing the role of Wladyslaw Szpilman in The Pianist?",
            "tags": [
                "acting",
                "academy_awards",
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "62573ef39da29df7b05f737f",
            "correctAnswer": "The Matrix",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring",
                "Seven",
                "The Big Lebowski"
            ],
            "question": "Name the movie that matches the following plot summary: 'A hacker discovers the life he knows is the elaborate deception of an evil cyber-intelligence.'",
            "tags": [
                "film",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951af9",
            "correctAnswer": "Scooby Doo",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Spongebob Squarepants",
                "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",
                "South Park"
            ],
            "question": "In Which Cartoon Might You Encounter 'The Mystery Machine'?",
            "tags": [
                "cartoons",
                "tv",
                "general_knowledge",
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95044a",
            "correctAnswer": "Holiday Inn",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Miracle on 34th Street",
                "It's a Wonderful Life",
                "White Christmas"
            ],
            "question": "From which film do we get the song 'White Christmas''",
            "tags": [
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950204",
            "correctAnswer": "Richard Donner",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Steven Spielberg",
                "Woody Allen",
                "Martin Scorsese"
            ],
            "question": "Which director directed Superman?",
            "tags": [
                "film_and_tv"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "regions": [],
            "isNiche": false
        }
    ];
